<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application</string>
    <string name="google_map_api_key">AIzaSyDp0__4uG-xE0T-gnbq1t4MJygHy3GHp_o</string>

    //starling
    <string name="starling">Starling</string>
    <string name="starling_des">Cook your pasta until al dente
\nSaute’ garlic in olive oil until fragrant
\nAdd cream cheese, pasta cooking water, parmesan, and stir well
\nDrain and add pasta to the skillet
\nToss until well combined, adding some pasta water if needed</string>


    //Tit
    <string name="Tit">Tit</string>
    <string name="Tit_des">The tits, chickadees, and titmice constitute the Paridae,
        \na large family of small passerine birds which occur
        \nmainly in the Northern Hemisphere and Africa.
        \nMost were formerly classified in the genus Parus</string>


    //Wrens
    <string name="Wrens">Wrens</string>
    <string name="Wrens_des">Wrens are a family of brown passerine
        \nbirds in the predominantly New World family Troglodytidae.
        \nThe family includes 88 species divided into 19 genera.
        \nOnly the Eurasian wren occurs in the Old World, where, in Anglophone regions,
        \nit is commonly known simply as the "wren", as it is the originator of the name.</string>


    //eurasian_chaffinch
    <string name="eurasian_chaffinch">Eurasian_chaffinch</string>
    <string name="eurasian_chaffinch_des">The Eurasian chaffinch, common chaffinch,
        \nor simply the chaffinch is a common and widespread small passerine
        \nbird in the finch family.
        \nThe male is brightly coloured with a blue-grey cap and rust-red underparts</string>



    //bird1
    <string name="bird1">Bird 1</string>
    <string name="bird1_des">A songbird is a bird belonging to the suborder Passeri
        \nof the perching birds.
        \nAnother name that is sometimes seen as the scientific or
        \nvernacular name is Oscines, from Latin oscen, "songbird"</string>


    //Flinches
    <string name="Flinches">Flinches</string>
    <string name="flinches_DES">The true finches are small to medium-sized passerine
        \nbirds in the family Fringillidae.
        \nFinches generally have stout conical bills adapted
        \nfor eating seeds and nuts and often have colourful plumage.
        \nThey occupy a great range of habitats where they are usually resident and do not migrate</string>


    //fries
    <string name="green_tit">Green_tita</string>
    <string name="green_tit_des">Tit Great tit
        \nGreat tit
        \nThe great tit is a passerine bird in the tit family Paridae.
        \nIt is a widespread and common species throughout Europe,
        \nthe Middle East, Central Asia and east across the Palearctic to the Amur River, .</string>
</resources>